Arun Sunny

Profile

Dedicated Technical Support Analyst with knowledge of service delivery and proven multitasking abilities. Solid team player with an outgoing, positive demeanor and proven skills in establishing rapport with clients. Specialize in quality, speed, and process optimization. Articulate, energetic, and results-oriented with exemplary passion for developing relationships, cultivating partnerships, and growing businesses.

Employment History

IT Support Analyst, Kian Computers, North York

FEBRUARY 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

- Handled all Customer Service and Support calls and emails.
- Worked to motivate and support all creative staff, resulting in excellent workflow and productivity.
- Helped to devise a new business model, and steps to support it.
- Created, resolved, or escalated support tickets.
- Managed front-end and back-end development in the company's Portfolio Analyst, Employee Track, and Account Management systems.

Technical Support Analyst, REXA, Toronto

DECEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

- Providing technical support and assistance to all REXA direct employees
- Troubleshooting all REXA provided hardware devices and business applications.
- Documenting Problems and solutions thoroughly and escalating service tickets to appropriate groups.
- Settled any customer disputes in a professional and pleasant manner.
- Worked to ensure a positive and hassle-free customer experience.

Education

Advanced Diploma , George Brown College, Toronto

SEPTEMBER 2018 — PRESENT

Computer Programming Analyst

Diploma, G-Tech Information Center, Mananthavady

JULY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

AutoCAD, Adobe Photoshop

Details

North York, M2J1L9 Canada 6478691231 sunnylistax25@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

GitHub

Skills

Python

Pandas

NumPy

TensorFlow

scikit-learn

Matplotlib

Jupyter Notebook

Google Collab

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

Supervised Learning

Unsupervised Learning

Data Visualization

GitHub

Git

Microsoft Power BI

MySQL

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

MongoDB

React

Node.js

Java